{
  "defaultLogs": [
    {
      "time": "2020-01-06T10:20:30Z",
      "health": {
        "heartRate": 145,
        "hoursSleep": 4.5
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Severity of the attack",
          "response": "5"
        },
        {
          "question": "What symptoms did you experience?",
          "response": "Agression,Extreme Irritation"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "time": "2020-01-08T10:20:30Z",
      "health": {
        "heartRate": 145,
        "hoursSleep": 4.5
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Severity of the attack",
          "response": "5"
        },
        {
          "question": "What symptoms did you experience?",
          "response": "Insomnia,Extreme Irritation"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "time": "2020-02-06T10:20:30Z",
      "health": {
        "heartRate": 145,
        "hoursSleep": 4.5
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Severity of the attack",
          "response": "5"
        },
        {
          "question": "What symptoms did you experience?",
          "response": "Insomnia,Suicidal Thoughts"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "time": "2020-02-11T10:20:30Z",
      "health": {
        "heartRate": 145,
        "hoursSleep": 4.5
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Severity of the attack",
          "response": "5"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "time": "2020-02-14T10:20:30Z",
      "health": {
        "heartRate": 145,
        "hoursSleep": 4.5
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Severity of the attack",
          "response": "3"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "time": "2020-02-17T10:20:30Z",
      "health": {
        "heartRate": 145,
        "hoursSleep": 4.5
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Severity of the attack",
          "response": "4"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "time": "2020-02-19T10:20:30Z",
      "health": {
        "heartRate": 145,
        "hoursSleep": 4.5
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Severity of the attack",
          "response": "3"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "time": "2020-02-21T10:20:30Z",
      "health": {
        "heartRate": 145,
        "hoursSleep": 4.5
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Severity of the attack",
          "response": "2"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "time": "2020-02-20T10:20:30Z",
      "health": {
        "heartRate": 145,
        "hoursSleep": 4.5
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Severity of the attack",
          "response": "2"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "time": "2020-02-22T10:20:30Z",
      "health": {
        "heartRate": 145,
        "hoursSleep": 4.5
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Severity of the attack",
          "response": "1"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "time": "2020-02-25T10:20:30Z",
      "health": {
        "heartRate": 145,
        "hoursSleep": 4.5
      },
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Severity of the attack",
          "response": "1"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}